Happy Gilmore returns!
Happy Gilmore 2 is a comedy film directed by Kyle Newacheck.
Happy Gilmore isn't done with golf — not by a long shot.
Since his retirement after his first Tour Championship win, Gilmore
returns to finance his daughter's ballet classes.
Happy Gilmore, played by Adam Sandler.
Virginia, played by Julie Bowen.
Shooter McGavin, played by Christopher McDonald.
Frank Manatee, played by Benny Safdie.
Hal L, played by Ben Stiller.
Oscar Mejías, played by Bad Bunny.
Happy Gilmore 2 is a 2025 American sports comedy film serving as a
sequel to Happy Gilmore (1996), and starring Adam Sandler.
It was written and produced by Sandler and Tim
Herlihy, and directed by Kyle Newacheck.
Sandler, Julie Bowen, Christopher McDonald, and Ben Stiller reprise their roles from
the original film, while Benny Safdie and Bad Bunny star in new roles.
The film follows Happy Gilmore returning to professional golf to help pay for his daughter's
overseas ballet school following his wife's death that led him to relapse into alcoholism.
Filming took place in New Jersey from September to December 2024.
Happy Gilmore 2 was released onto Netflix on July
25, 2025, and received mixed reviews.
The film explores themes of golf, sequel,
duringcreditsstinger, introspective, whimsical.
The tone is lighthearted.